crypto-bridge.org 2019-12-02

# cryptobridge.github.io | Gateway to Decentralized Trading

Liquidblocks ApS ("the Company" or "we") is the operator of the websites https://crypto-bridge.org/ and https://wallet.crypto-bridge.org/ (the "Websites"). The Company collects and processes personal data of individuals (the "User" or "you") using the Websites and the services offered through these Websites. The protection and confidentiality of your personal data is of particular importance to us. We treat your personal data confidentially and in accordance with the applicable data protection laws, in particular with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (the "GDPR").

The use of our Websites is generally possible without providing personal data; notwithstanding the collection of data for the provisioning of the Websites, please note that the storage of the data in logfiles is mandatory for the operation of the Websites. Insofar as personal data (e.g. name, address or e-mail addresses or other data) are collected on our Websites, this data will not be passed on to third parties.

In the following, we will tell you what data is collected during your visit to our Websites, as well as the legal bases for the processing of personal data, the purpose of the data processing, its use, the duration of the storage and your rights. We collect and use the personal data of our users only insofar as this is necessary for the provision of a functional website as well as our content and services.

This Privacy Policy applies to:

  * Visitors to our Websites;
  * Users making use of the Company's gateway services via a BitShares account;
  * Developers making use of the Company's listing services.

## I. Name and address of the responsible body

The responsible body (the "Controller") within the meaning of the GDPR is:

Liquidblocks ApS, a company incorporated under the laws of Denmark, with a registered office at Gl. Kongevej 60, 1850 Frederiksberg, Denmark.

Website: <https://crypto-bridge.org/>

If you have any questions relating to data processing in connection with our Websites and services offered through these websites, and your rights according to the applicable data protection laws, you may contact us by email: [info@crypto-bridge.org](mailto:info@crypto-bridge.org)

## II. Provisioning of the Websites and Creation of Logfiles

The provider of the Websites automatically collects and stores information in so-called server log files, which your browser automatically transmits to us. Such information is needed to establish a connection to the Websites. The processed information is:

  * browser type and browser version;
  * operating system used;
  * the internet service provider of the user;
  * the IP address of the user;
  * hostname of the accessing computer;
  * time of the server inquiry;
  * websites from which the user's system reaches our Websites;
  * websites accessed by the user's system via our Websites.

The data is also stored in the log files of our system. These data are not stored together with other personal data of the user and is not combined with other data sources.

The legal basis for processing of the data is Art. 6 (1)(f) GDPR. The logfiles are processed for technical and administrative purposes of establishing and maintaining a connection in order to guarantee the security and functionality of our Websites and to be able to prosecute any illegal attacks on it if necessary. We reserve the right to review this data at a later date if we become aware of specific indications of illegal use.

Our legitimate interest in data processing pursuant to Art. 6 (1)(f) GDPR results from the security interest mentioned and the necessity of a trouble-free provision of our Websites.

Data will be stored until 1 year from the moment of collecting for security reasons.

## III Cookies

Some websites use so-called cookies. Cookies do not cause any damage to your computer and do not contain viruses. Cookies are used to make our Websites more user-friendly, effective and secure. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer and saved by your browser. Cookies contain a characteristic string of characters that allows the browser to be uniquely identified when you return to the Websites.

Some elements of our Websites require that the calling browser can be identified even after a page change. The following data is stored and transmitted in the cookies:

  * language settings;
  * log-in-information;
  * frequency of page views;
  * use of website functions

Such data collected by cookies will be pseudonymised through appropriate technical measures. It is therefore no longer possible to assign the data to the calling user. The data is not stored together with other personal data of users.

The legal basis for the processing of personal data using cookies is Art. 6 (1)(f) GDPR.

Most of the cookies we use are so-called "session cookies". They will automatically be deleted at the end of your visit. Other cookies remain stored on your device until you delete them. These cookies enable us to recognize your browser the next time you visit our Websites.

You can set your browser in such a way that you are informed about the setting of cookies and allow cookies only in individual cases, you can exclude the acceptance of cookies for certain cases or generally and you can activate the automatic deletion of cookies when closing the browser. When cookies are disabled, the functionality of our Websites may be limited.

## IV. Google Analytics

This Websites use the functions of the web analytics service Google Analytics. Provider is Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.

Google Analytics uses so-called "cookies". These are text files that are stored on your computer and allow an analysis of your use of the website. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is usually transferred to a Google server in the United States of America and stored there.

Google Inc. will use this information to evaluate your use of our Websites, to compile reports on website activity and to provide other services associated with the use of the website and the Internet. Google may also transfer this information to third parties if required by law or if third parties process this data on behalf of Google.

For more information on how we handle user data at Google Analytics, please see the Google Privacy Policy: https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en

You can prevent the storage of cookies by setting your browser software accordingly; however, we would like to point out that in this case you may not be able to use all the functions of these Websites in full. You can also prevent Google from collecting the data generated by the cookie and relating to your use of the website (including your IP address) and from processing this data by Google by downloading and installing the browser plugin available under the following link: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en

Opposition to data collection

You can prevent Google Analytics from collecting your information by clicking on the link below. An opt-out cookie is set to prevent your data from being collected when you visit this website in the future: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en.

Demographic features in Google Analytics

These Websites use the "demographic features" feature of Google Analytics. This allows reports to be created that contain information about the age, gender and interests of the visitors to the site. This data originates from Google's interest-based advertising and visitor data from third-party providers. This data cannot be assigned to a specific person. You can disable this feature at any time through your Google Account's ad settings or disallow the collection of your information by Google Analytics as shown in the "Disclaimer" section.

## V. Create and Use BitShares Accounts via our Websites

On our Websites, we offer users the opportunity to create or login via a BitShares account by providing personal data. The data is entered into an input mask. With every account creation and login into such an account, a connection to the blockchain-based decentralized crypto asset exchange BitShares ("BitShares") is made. The scope and purpose of the data collection and the further processing and use of the data by BitShares, as well as the rights and options for privacy protection in this respect, can be found in the respective BitShares' privacy policy: https://bitshares.org/privacy-policy.html. Neither the Company (or any person or legal entity affiliated with the Company) nor its gateway have any control over or influence on how BitShares uses, stores or otherwise processes users' personal data. We have no influence on it and cannot provide you with any information in this regard due to a lack of knowledge.

During the account creation or login process we collect the following data:

  * Username;
  * Public key;
  * IP address of the calling computer/user;
  * Date and time of login.

Such data is also stored at the time of account creation or during login process on servers operated by AWS located in Frankfurt, Germany.

The legal basis for the processing of the data after account creation or login on our Websites by the user is Art. 6 (1)(b) GDPR.

A user account, including its creation and login process, is necessary to carry out pre-contractual measures and to conclude and execute the contracts relating to the Company's gateway services. The data collected is the minimum required data we need to create your user profile as well as conduct user verification for security reasons. Without the data processing described in this section, we cannot execute the contract.

Data will be stored until 1 year after closing of the account for security reasons.

## VI. Use of Gateway Services and Listing

On our Websites, we offer users the opportunity to use our gateway services, deposit and withdrawals of crypto assets, after login via a BitShares account. The data entered pertaining to a deposit or withdrawal is registered on BitShares and stored.

We process the following data at the time of gateway use:

  * IP address of the calling computer/user;
  * date and time of gateway usage;
  * time and date, amounts, types of crypto assets subject to withdrawal or deposit.
  * We also offer Users the opportunity to list crypto assets via our gateway. When interacting with us to facilitate the listing, we process the following data:
  * IP address of the calling computer/user;
  * E-mail address;
  * Twitter handle
  * Discord handle
  * Company name (optional)
  * date and time of interaction with company
  * Type of crypto asset, information on developers, code

The legal basis for the processing of the data is Art. 6 (1)(b) GDPR.

Storing such data during the conclusion of contracts to deposit, withdraw or list crypto assets is necessary to conclude and execute the contracts relating to the Company's gateway services.

Data will be stored until 1 year after closing of the account for security reasons.

Data (except for the IP address) is disclosed to the software provider Atlassian and stored on their servers being located in the European Union as well as in the third countries U.S. and Australia. Any data transfers to third countries comply with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and/or is carried out on the basis of European Commission Standard Contractual Clauses pursuant to Art. 46 (1)(c) GDPR. For more information see: https://www.atlassian.com/legal/data-processing-addendum.

Some data will also be included in the processing made by BitShares. We have no influence on data processing by BitShares and cannot provide you with any information in this regard due to a lack of knowledge.The scope and purpose of the data collection and the further processing and use of the data by BitShares, as well as the rights and options for privacy protection in this respect, can be found in the respective BitShare's privacy policy: https://bitshares.org/privacy-policy.html. Neither the Company (or any person or legal entity affiliated with the Company) nor its gateway have any control over or influence on how BitShares uses, stores or otherwise processes the users' personal data. We have no influence on it and cannot provide you with any information in this regard due to a lack of knowledge.

## VII. Know Your Customer

On our Websites, we ask users to register by providing personal data in a know your customer process through the third-party software provider Fractal Blockchain GmbH ("Fractal") as a white-label solution. The process is carried out according to the relevant European Union law, notably Directives 2018/843/EU and 2015/849/EU and as well as Directives 2009/138/EC and 2013/36/EU, and relevant Danish anti-money laundering and counter terrorist financing legislation. We obtain this information from you for security and verification purposes to provide our services to you.

Fractal, on our behalf stores and processes the technical information of your device which you use for orders and communication - cell phone, tablet, notebook, personal computer, etc. (e.g. IP address) and login information (e-mail address, password).

Fractal is located in Germany, stores this data in secured servers in the EU and process this information in compliance with the applicable data protection law(s).

For more information, you can reach out to their person responsible for data protection at privacy@fractal.id, for support in the KYC journey support@fractal.id.

The legal basis for such processing is Art. 6 (1)(c) GDPR and necessary for our performance of contract according to Art. 6(1)(b) GDPR. The participation in the know your customer process and the data processing necessary is essential to carry out pre-contractual measures and to conclude and execute the contract.

We clarify that the provisioning of personal data is partly required by law (e.g. tax regulations, relevant EU and Danish anti-money laundering and counter terrorist financing legislation) or can also result from contractual provisions (e.g. information on the contractual partner). Sometimes it may be necessary to conclude a contract that the data subject provides us with personal data, which must subsequently be processed by Fractal. The data subject may be obliged to provide us with personal data when concluding a contract with us. The non-provisioning of the personal data would lead to non-conclusion of contract and subsequently exclude the user from the use of services offered by the Company.

The data is entered into the know your customer input mask, transmitted to Fractal and stored with Fractal. The following data is processed during such process for natural persons:

  * first name, last name;
  * CPR number (for Danish individuals) / ID or passport number;
  * place of residence/address;
  * verification of address against certain documents;
  * photo from copy of ID or passport;
  * birth date;
  * email address;
  * customer as a politically exposed person (PEP);
  * origin of funds.

In case the user is a legal entity, the following data is processed during such process:

  * company registration documentation;
  * information on the ultimate beneficial owner, i.e. the natural person ultimately benefiting from the legal entity’s business activity (see information required for natural persons above).

As assessed on a case-by-case basis, additional data may be asked of the User.

For all users participating in the know your customer process we only store a reference number provided by Fractal to indicate in our database that you carried out such know your customer process and link back to the data set processed by Fractal.

Data will be deleted as soon as the purpose for which it was collected and processed, and all commercial and tax law retention obligations are fulfilled.

## VII. E-mail contact

It is possible to contact us via the following email address: info@crypto-bridge.org. The personal data of the user transmitted by email will be stored. Such data will not be passed on to third parties. The data will only be used for the processing of the conversation.

The legal basis for the processing is Art. 6 (1)(f) GDPR.

The storage of data is necessary for communication with you being the legitimate interest in data processing pursuant to Art. 6 (1)(f) GDPR. The data will be deleted as soon as it is no longer necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was collected. This is the case when the respective conversation with the user has ended. The conversation ends when the circumstances indicate that the matter in question has been conclusively clarified. The additional personal data collected during the sending process will be deleted after the it is no longer necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was collected.

## IX. Integration Of Third-Party Services And Content

Insofar as we integrate third-party content on our Websites, such as videos from Youtube or content from other websites, the possibility to consume such content via our website presupposes that your IP address is transmitted to the providers of such content ("third-party providers"). Otherwise, this content cannot not be sent to your browser. The IP address is therefore required for the presentation of this content. We make every effort to use only those contents whose respective providers use the IP address solely for sending the integrated contents. If a third party provider stores your IP address for other purposes, e.g. for statistical purposes, we have no influence on it and cannot provide you with any information in this regard due to a lack of knowledge.

## X. References to Company's Social Media Accounts

Our Websites refer to the Company's social media accounts on

Discord Community, 1180 1901 S Bascom Ave, Campbell, US (HQ), privacy policy at <https://discordapp.com/privacy>;

Twitter, Twitter Inc., One Cumberland Place, Fenian Street, Dublin 2, D02 AX07, Ireland, privacy policy at <https://twitter.com/en/privacy>; and

Reddit, 420 Taylor St, San Francisco, US (HQ), privacy policy at <https://www.redditinc.com/policies/privacy-policy-may-25-2018>.

When you access one of our social media accounts hosted by any of these three providers you leave our Websites. We have no influence on the amount of data that these providers collect and are not responsible for data collection by these providers. Please consult their respective privacy policies to learn more.

## XI. Your Rights in connection with processing of personal data

In the following, we inform you on your rights that you have in connection with the processing of personal data by us and may exercise according to the GDPR.

### 1\. Right of access

You have the right at any time to demand information on if we process your personal data. In the event of such processing, you may request the following information from us: (i) the purposes for which personal data are processed; (ii) the categories of personal data which are processed; (iii) the recipients or categories of recipients to whom your personal data have been or will be disclosed; (iv) the planned duration of the storage of your personal data or, if specific information is not possible, criteria for determining the storage duration; (v) the existence of a right to correct or delete your personal data, a right to restrict the processing by us or a right of objection to such processing; (vi) the existence of a right of appeal to a supervisory authority; (vii) all available information on the origin of the data if the personal data are not collected directly from you; (viii) the existence of automated decision-making, including profiling in accordance with Article 22 paragraph 1 and 4 GDPR and, at least in these cases, meaningful information on the logic involved and the scope and intended impact of such processing on you.

You have the right to request information on whether your personal data are transferred to a third country or to an international organisation. In this context, you may request to be informed on the appropriate guarantees in connection with the transfer of data.

### 2\. Right of rectification

You have the right to demand us to correct and/or complete your personal data if your personal data processed is incorrect or incomplete.

### 3\. Right to restrict processing

You may request to restrict the processing of your personal data if (i) you deny the accuracy of the personal data for a period of time that enables us to verify the accuracy of the personal data; (ii) the processing is unlawful and you refuse to delete the personal data and instead request the restriction of the use of the personal data; (iii) we no longer need your personal data for the purposes of processing, but you need them to assert, exercise or defend legal claims; (iv) if you have lodged an objection against the processing and it has not yet been determined whether the legitimate reasons of the person responsible outweigh your grounds.

### 4\. Right of deletion

You may demand your personal data to be deleted if (i) the personal data concerning you are no longer necessary for the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed; (ii) you revoke your consent to the processing and there is no other legal basis for the processing; (iii) you submit an objection to data processing and there are no predominant justifiable reasons for the processing; (iv) your personal data have been processed illegally; (v) the deletion of your personal data is necessary to fulfil a legal obligation under Union law or the law of the Member States to which we are subject.

### 5\. Right to data portability

You have the right to obtain your personal data in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. You have the right to transmit your data to another controller. Where technically feasible, you have the right to have your data transmitted directly from us to another controller.

### 6\. Right to object

On grounds relating to your particular situation, you have the right to object at any time to the processing of your personal data which is carried out on the basis of Article 6 paragraph 1 lit. f) GDPR. Such grounds exist, in particular, if they underline your interests and outweigh our interest in the respective data processing. If your personal data are processed in order to carry out direct advertising, you have the right to object at any time to the processing of personal data for the purpose of such advertising; this also applies to profiling, insofar as it is associated with such direct advertising.

### 7\. Right to revoke the declaration of consent under data protection law

If you gave us the consent to process your personal data, you have the right to revoke your declaration of consent at any time. The revocation of the consent does not affect the legality of the processing carried out based on the consent until the revocation.

### 8\. Right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority

You have the right to address the supervisory authority for any questions or complaints. The supervisory authority is Datatilsynet, Borgergade 28, DK-1300 Copenhagen K.

## XII. Changes To The Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to amend our Privacy Policy in order to adapt it to changes in the law or changes to the service and data processing. However, this applies solely with regard to declarations on data processing. If your consent is required or if parts of Privacy Policy contain regulations of the contractual relationship with you, changes will only be made with your consent.

You are asked to inform yourself regularly about the content of our Privacy Policy.
